meetgadget.com 2013-05-19

# Meet Gadget Privacy

MeetGadget's Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using MeetGadget. 

By using or accessing MeetGadget, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use MeetGadget. 

**Information We Collect and How We Use It**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that the collection of personal information is limited to that which is necessary to fulfill the purposes identified below. If we use your information in a manner different than the purpose for which it is collected, then we will ask you for your consent prior to such use.

**_Account information_** \- To take advantage of certain features offered on MeetGadget, such as uploading photos or videos, you need to create a User account. When creating a User account, we ask for and record personal information such as your name, email address and password. When creating a User profile, you may choose to include preferential options such as adding a personal photo. We use your email address to send you updates, news, service-related announcements and contact you on behalf of other Users (such as other Users who send you personal messages). You may choose not to receive e-mails of this type by updating your notification settings on your account, though MeetGadget reserves the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

**_Submissions_** \- We store your User profile information, as well as your name, photos, videos and other information you have chosen to display to people in the networks specified in your privacy settings. We store this information so that MeetGadget may present it back to you when you and others when accessing your User profile. Any personal information you voluntarily disclose online may be collected and used by others pursuant to your privacy settings.

**_Feedback_** \- If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any personal information and other content that you provide in your communication so that we can effectively respond to your communication. You do not need a User account to contact MeetGadget. Please understand that we are not obligated to compensate you for any feedback you provide.

**_Personal messaging_** \- In order to allow you to send and receive personal messages to other registered Users of MeetGadget, we record the messages that you send and receive.

**_Activity_** \- Whether or not you have a User account with MeetGadget, we record information relating to your use of MeetGadget, such as the profiles and gadgets your view, the searches you undertake, which other Users you communicate with, the frequency and size of data transfers, the information you display about yourself, the information you click on, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. If you are logged in, we may associate this information with your User account. We use this type of information to administer the Website and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of User behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Website. You cannot be identified from this aggregate information. 

**_Cookies_** \- We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of our service. The term "cookies" refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing the site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser help file directions.

**_Enforcement_** \- We may use the information we collect in connection with your use of MeetGadget (including your personal information) in order to investigate, enforce, and apply our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. 

**Information Made Available to the Public**

When you create a User account, some information about your User account and your account activity will be visible to other MeetGadget Users. This may include your User profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, and other personal information you voluntarily choose to disclose. You may limit the extent to which this information is accessed by adjusting your privacy settings.

Your name and profile picture thumbnail will be available in search results on the Website and those limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. This is primarily so your friends can find you and send a friend request. People who see your name in searches, however, will not be able to access your profile information unless you have allowed such access based on your privacy settings.

**Transfer of Information**

We may distribute your User-Generated Content to third parties, as permitted pursuant to our Terms of Service. The third parties may in turn publicly display or publish your submissions in connection with their own websites and media platforms. When we distribute your submissions to third parties, we typically include your account name (but not your personal information unless you include your personal information in your submissions).

We may share your personal information with third parties to provide you with services that we offer through the MeetGadget, conduct quality assurance testing, facilitate creation of accounts, provide technical and customer support. These third parties are required not to use your personal information other than to provide the services requested by you.

We may share your personal information with joint ventures or other companies under a common control (collectively, "Affiliates") that we may have now or in the future, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires our company or our assets, that company will possess your personal information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (b) enforce or apply our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy; (c) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order; or (d) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our Users, affiliates, or the public. Please note that we are not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that we receive.

We may disclose information in the aggregate to third parties relating to User behavior in connection with actual or prospective business relationship with those third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of Users that have been exposed to, or have clicked on, advertising banners, or number of users that have particular product.

We use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit MeetGadget. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Links**

MeetGadget may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with those third parties, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.

**Third Party Advertising**

Advertisements that appear on MeetGadget are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to Users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. MeetGadget does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on MeetGadget unless you choose to share it with them.

**_This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by MeetGadget and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers._**

**Controlling Your Personal Data**

Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to the information on your User profile, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your User profile and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that the User-Generated content you post on the Website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of your User-Generated Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User-Generated Content.

Please also note that the personal messages you send or receive using MeetGadget’s personal messaging feature are only private to the extent that you and the sender/recipient keep them private. For example, we do not have any control over whether a recipient of one of your personal messages publicly posts the contents of such a message.

As a registered MeetGadget User, you can edit your personal information and your privacy preferences at any time by accessing the "Profile" section of this Website. You can also terminate your User account at any time. Upon request for termination of your account, MeetGadget will use commercially reasonable efforts to close your account, and cease displaying your User-Generated Content on the Website, except for postings that have been shared with others on the Website such as but not limited to discussion comments or products that have become part MeetGadget’s database; nevertheless, we may still retain your personal information in our systems.

**Security**

Your account is password protected. We use industry standard measures to protect the personal information that is stored in our database. We limit the access to your personal information to those employees and contractors who need access to perform their job function, such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security on MeetGadget, please contact us at **[meetgadget@meetgadget.com](mailto:meetgadget@meetgadget.com)**. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that your personal information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

**_You hereby acknowledge that MeetGadget is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner._**

**E-mails and Opt-out**

You may opt-out of receiving personal messages from specific Users by changing the notification settings under the “Account” tab after you log on to MeetGadget Unregistered Users who receive e-mails from us may also opt-out of receiving further e-mails by following the instructions contained in our e-mails.

**Terms of Service, Notices and Revisions**

Your use of MeetGadget, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Service and all of its dispute resolution provisions including limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. Your continued use of MeetGadget indicates your agreement to these changes. It is solely your responsible to check for updates of this policy. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**Contacting the Website**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this Website, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at **[meetgadget@meetgadget.com](mailto:meetgadget@meetgadget.com)**
